<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 14:32:37 +0200</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Biggar]]></title><url><![CDATA[biggar]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Biggar]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template-case-studies.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[case-studies]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;col-lg-5&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;A customer from back in 2006 got in contact wondering if I was still doing landscaping.&amp;nbsp; Since then of course, GM Land solutions had grown and had a lot more equimpent.&amp;nbsp; The customer was struggling to find someone that would take on a full project, including a lot of specialised tree surgery, building steps, digger work and a large area of paving, without having to go to different businesses and try to arrange them all seperately.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;GM Land solutions were able to take on all the work, inhouse, and stage it all in a way that worked for the progression of the job, and for the customer.&amp;nbsp; This also would have worked out cheaper than outsourcing other aspects of the work, IE a landscaper getting in a tree surgeon and hiring in plant etc, as we had all that was required and all the right skills and expertese to complete the works.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;There were trees next to a wall, and road that had to be carefull dismantled and cleared away qickly to cause minimal disruption to the traffic.&amp;nbsp; As required by law, we were able to provide 2 qualified climbers (as is always needed for safety reasons), one of wholm was Gavin Mathison, the proprietor, who also layed all the paving on another part of the project.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;The paving was a large area, and had to be a product the tied into the colour and style of the old sandstone house.&amp;nbsp; Following a few discussions it was agreed to use the red/brown indian sandstone, of mixed sizes, which is also a natural stone product.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-lg-7&quot;&gt;
	&lt;h2&gt;Before&lt;/h2&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/case-studies/biggar/before-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/case-studies/biggar/before-2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;h2&gt;During&lt;/h2&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/case-studies/biggar/during-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;h2&gt;After&lt;/h2&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/case-studies/biggar/after-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/case-studies/biggar/after-2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/case-studies/biggar/after-3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[gmlandsolutions]]></author></item>
