<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 17:11:43 +0200</pubDate><title><![CDATA[About GM Land Solutions]]></title><url><![CDATA[about]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[About]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[5]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[Y]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;GM Land Solutions (formerly Tweeddale Groundcare) was set up in 2004 by Gavin Mathison.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Based near Peebles in the Scottish Borders, we work covering a wide area across the borders, Edinburgh, and surrounding areas.&amp;nbsp;Contractors include Edinburgh City council.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;GM Land Solutions cover a wide range of different work, from small jobs, to maintenance work to large scale design and build landscaping projects. Details of some of the services we offer can be found in the services section of the website.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;We recycle wherever possible, and even hire in a mobile crusher to crush waste stone and concrete that is stockpiled from jobs, and then re-use this material.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;GM Land Solutions have various different tools and machinery to carry out many different jobs, this makes jobs run smoother and more efficiently, and also keeps the costs down for the customer as opposed to having to hire in as much equipment.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;For those people doing DIY projects, or other businesses reading this, we offer a wide selection of tools and machinery for hire at very competitive rates, for short or long term hire. Please take a look at the &lt;a href=&quot;plant-hire&quot;&gt;Plant Hire section&lt;/a&gt; of the website for further information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:8888/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/about.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[gmlandsolutions]]></author></item>
