<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 13:52:29 +0200</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Groundwork]]></title><url><![CDATA[groundwork]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Groundwork]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[services]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-7&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years of investing in plant and training, we now carry out more groundwork as well as landscaping, this could be anything from creating shed bases, drainage, digging founds, re-shaping areas of ground or garden prior to landscaping, forestry/farm roads etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a job in January 2014 to create a shed base in a hill side at Thornielee, Near Galashiels for a 90 ft long shed.&amp;nbsp; This involved digging into the hill and infilling, to create a area wide enough.&amp;nbsp; We then had to put in drainage to take the water from the hill away from running into the shed, and hardcore and roll the area ready for construction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We now have a 7.5Ton digger for larger jobs, and can source larger machines still for even bigger projects.&amp;nbsp; We have smaller plant including a Micro digger that is small enough to fit through a gap or doorway of 70cm!&amp;nbsp; We have a tractor and access to various implements for then making good ground and seeding etc after work is complete.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Why not &lt;a href=&quot;contact&quot;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; to discuss your ideas or to arrange a free, no obligation, quote?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-5&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/services/groundwork/groundwork-1.jpg&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/gmlandsolutions/data/uploads/services/groundwork/groundwork-2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[gmlandsolutions]]></author></item>
